<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="zh-CN" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title> 老蔣 LAO JIANG - 最新博客</title>
  <updated>2024-11-13T23:37:04+11:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name> 老蔣 LAO JIANG</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/exciting-news-were-almost-there</id>
    <published>2024-11-13T23:37:04+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-11-13T23:42:35+11:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/exciting-news-were-almost-there"/>
    <title>Exciting News – We&apos;re Almost There!</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lao Jiang</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>I’m so thrilled to share that we’re just a few steps away from bringing you our very first batch of crispy chilli oil! It’s been an exciting journey, and the last two months have been all about hard work and careful planning. From updating our chilli oil label, sourcing ingredients and suppliers, trialling different jar shapes and sizes, to finalising our food licence registration—it’s been a lot of work, but totally worth it!</p>
<p>Super stoked with how the labels and jars have turned out! There are a couple of small tweaks we’ll make for the next print run, but it’s pretty much exactly what we had in mind. We can’t wait to start production and, most importantly, share our beloved crispy chilli oil with you all!</p>
<p>For our first batch, we’ve set ourselves a goal to make—and fingers crossed, sell—100 jars of crispy chilli oil! Stay tuned for more updates in our next post. In the meantime, follow us on IG and TikTok at <strong>@laojiangcooks</strong> for all the latest!</p>
<p> </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/six-months-later-finding-my-way-back</id>
    <published>2024-07-19T22:54:04+10:00</published>
    <updated>2024-07-19T22:56:27+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/six-months-later-finding-my-way-back"/>
    <title>六个月后……找到回归之路</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lao Jiang</name>
    </author>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<meta charset="utf-8">
<p data-mce-fragment="1">经过六个月寻找解决方案而没有取得太大进展之后，我终于找到了项目所需的突破。</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">在过去的六个月里，我努力在当地议会区域寻找一个可供出租的商业厨房，因此进展停滞不前。我从未想到这个障碍会阻碍我的进步。这让我考虑在另一个议会注册以使用他们的商业厨房，但我一直想留在当地。在另一个议会注册企业的麻烦在于，这需要我申请在当地销售的许可证，并且没有资格参加议会定期举办的商业网络研讨会。</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">今晚，在几个月没有查看电子邮件之后，我登录了邮箱，惊讶地发现了一封来自市议会的电子邮件。这封邮件是二月份发的，里面透露了一个隐藏的宝藏——我家附近有一个可以出租的商业厨房！</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">这一发现重新点燃了我的动力。现在，我可以继续办理食品经营许可证，并清楚地看到了成为注册食品企业的途径。</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">这次经历提醒了我两件重要的事情：定期检查我的电子邮件，永远不要再让无所作为阻碍我。</p>
<p data-mce-fragment="1">继续加油！下次更新前请保持温暖，保持健康。</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/week-1</id>
    <published>2023-12-10T19:54:39+11:00</published>
    <updated>2024-07-19T23:00:22+10:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/week-1"/>
    <title>第 1 周 - 入门</title>
    <author>
      <name>Lao Jiang</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[关注我们的每周博客，了解我们冒险的最新动态。<p><a class="read-more" href="https://laojiangcooks.com/zh/blogs/news/week-1">更多</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>本周标志着一段激动人心的旅程的开始，我深入收集了有关我爸爸的脆辣椒油的更多信息和反馈。我们取得了很大的进步，最近建立了一个 Shopify 网站来记录旅程并将其与调查联系起来 - 经过一些 YouTube 浏览后我们选择了 Jotform，它超级简单而且免费！</p>
<p>接下来，我们从“老江厨师”作为品牌名称开始，并反复讨论，最终选定“老江”，并添加了“做脆皮辣椒油”的口号。如果您想知道老蒋这个名字的由来？这是汉语“老蒋”的直译，也是我父亲的朋友们亲切地称呼他的名字，“蒋”是我们的姓氏。</p>
<p>就我而言，创建品牌标志是最难的部分，因为我不太懂艺术，尽管我很清楚我希望汉字成为焦点。在尝试了一些 AI 徽标网站后，我们最终使用 Canva 创建了一个简单的圆形徽标，毫无疑问，这在我们的后期旅程中需要一些专业的帮助。</p>
<p>感觉很有成就感，并准备好下周进行更多产品测试，并且一如既往，很高兴听到您对我们目前进展情况的想法和评论。</p>
<p>姜爸爸这周签退了。</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
